{"questionlist":[
{"cardfront":"A",
"cardback":"a"
},
{"cardfront":"B",
"cardback":"b"
},
{"cardfront":"C",
"cardback":"c"
},
{"cardfront":"D",
"cardback":"d"
},
{"cardfront":"E",
"cardback":"e"
},
{"cardfront":"F",
"cardback":"f"
},
{"cardfront":"G",
"cardback":"g"
},
{"cardfront":"H",
"cardback":"h"
},
{"cardfront":"I",
"cardback":"i"
},
{"cardfront":"J",
"cardback":"j"
},
{"cardfront":"K",
"cardback":"k"
},
{"cardfront":"L",
"cardback":"l"
},
{"cardfront":"M",
"cardback":"m"
},
{"cardfront":"N",
"cardback":"n"
},
{"cardfront":"O",
"cardback":"o"
},
{"cardfront":"P",
"cardback":"p"
},
{"cardfront":"Q",
"cardback":"q"
},
{"cardfront":"R",
"cardback":"r"
},
{"cardfront":"S",
"cardback":"s"
},
{"cardfront":"T",
"cardback":"t"
},
{"cardfront":"U",
"cardback":"u"
},
{"cardfront":"V",
"cardback":"v"
},
{"cardfront":"W",
"cardback":"w"
},
{"cardfront":"X",
"cardback":"x"
},
{"cardfront":"Y",
"cardback":"y"
},
{"cardfront":"Z",
"cardback":"z"
},
{"cardfront":"0",
"cardback":"0"
},
{"cardfront":"1",
"cardback":"1"
},
{"cardfront":"2",
"cardback":"2"
},
{"cardfront":"3",
"cardback":"3"
},
{"cardfront":"4",
"cardback":"4"
},
{"cardfront":"5",
"cardback":"5"
},
{"cardfront":"6",
"cardback":"6"
},
{"cardfront":"7",
"cardback":"7"
},
{"cardfront":"8",
"cardback":"8"
},
{"cardfront":"9",
"cardback":"9"
}
]}
